we also have effects that we can apply to our image so if I click on it and wait
so as you see we have plenty of effect categories, we have scenes, warm winter,
retro, vintage, you know, filmatic and any of them that has this kind of triangle on it
this means that it is for the kind of a pro plan and pro pricing so you need to upgrade your account
or something like that and yes what else do we have so for example with this let's say
which one? with this classic one right so in the classic form we have plenty of effects you know
so these are effect categories each of them and if you open each up you'll see plenty and plenty
of available effects for that very category and by clicking on each we'll be able to apply it
right so as you see I can for example use this one you know and it's applied to my image as easy as
that and by clicking apply it will apply and if I cancel it it will be cancelled and we also have the
intensity of that effect which is a percentage and we can set so I click cancel